<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<force id="10" lang="en-gb"  xmlns="http://www.npia.police.uk/cm09/npt"><name><![CDATA[Northumbria Police]]></name><url><![CDATA[http://www.northumbria.police.uk]]></url><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pledge><![CDATA[<p>The police service in England and Wales will support law abiding citizens and pursue criminals relentlessly to keep you and your neighbourhoods safe from harm.</p><p>We will:</p><p>Treat you fairly, with respect and provide accessible services when you need them.</p><p><br /> Tell you who your Neighbourhood Policing Team is and how you can contact them.</p><p><br /> Ensure police patrols in your area are where and when you say you need them most.</p><p><br /> Respond promptly to all messages to your Neighbourhood Policing Team.</p><p><br /> Attend emergencies immediately, giving an estimated arrival time.</p><p><br /> Answer non-emergency calls promptly and provide a policing response to meet your needs.</p><p><br /> Arrange regular public meetings with your Neighbourhood Policing Team to discuss those things important to you.</p><p><br /> Provide monthly updates about what we are doing with our partners to make your neighbourhood safer.</p><p><br /> Agree with victims how often we will update you about your case and for how long.</p><p><br /> Respond promptly to any report of poor service and agree how it will be handled.</p><p><br /> We want to do our best for you. If we fail to meet our Policing Pledge we will always explain why we have not met the high standards we aim for and you deserve.&nbsp;</p>]]></pledge><crest-url><![CDATA[]]></crest-url><engagement-methods><method><title><![CDATA[Facebook]]></title><description><![CDATA[Follow us on Facebook]]></description><url><![CDATA[http://www.facebook.com/northumbriapolice]]></url></method><method><title><![CDATA[Twitter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Follow us on Twitter]]></description><url><![CDATA[http://www.twitter.com/northumbriapol]]></url></method><method><title><![CDATA[YouTube]]></title><description><![CDATA[Follow us on YouTube]]></description><url><![CDATA[http://www.youtube.com/wwwnorthumbriapolice]]></url></method></engagement-methods>

</force>
